{
    "id": "a5c5d3c340284d7da6ebd305c86324e2",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………….. she know what she is doing?",
            "description": "She is singular subject. Hence, we use does here.",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Did",
                "Does"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………… forget to give me a call before you leave.",
            "description": "The simple present is used in imperative sentences. In imperatives the subject is you.",
            "answers": [
                "Did not",
                "Does not",
                "Don't"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… your shoes before entering the temple.",
            "description": "The simple present is used in imperative sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "Removes",
                "Remove",
                "Removed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………. harder than anybody I know.",
            "description": "We use the simple present to talk about facts.",
            "answers": [
                "works",
                "is working",
                "worked"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He was a true patriot who …………………….. for his country.",
            "description": "When the verb in the main clause is in the past tense, we use a past tense in the subordinate clause as well.",
            "answers": [
                "would die",
                "will die",
                "has died"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………… my grandparents every Sunday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visited",
                "visit",
                "am visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Sam ………………………. a good job.",
            "description": "The present perfect is used to give news.",
            "answers": [
                "has to find",
                "will found",
                "has found"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………………… the job by Monday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would finish",
                "will have finished",
                "will be finishing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t phone them now. They …………………………. dinner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will be having",
                "would be having",
                "shall be having"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………. to him for thirty years.",
            "description": "We use the present perfect to talk about life experiences up to now.",
            "answers": [
                "is seeing married",
                "has seen married",
                "have seen married"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Somebody has ……………………… my purse?",
            "description": "Stolen is the past participle of steal.",
            "answers": [
                "stolen",
                "stole",
                "stealed",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………….. to anyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has never apologized",
                "never apologized"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}